imageevent.com 2013-05-23

# ImageEvent Privacy Policy

**ImageEvent Privacy Policy**

At ImageEvent have a firm commitment to safeguarding the privacy of our customers. We are very concerned about your privacy, and we make sure that your information is protected. We want you to be able to enjoy ImageEvent experience safely and privately. 

**Your ImageEvent account**  
When you sign up with ImageEvent, you establish a password-protected personal account for storing your digital images. You and you alone control who may visit the images stored in your ImageEvent account. Your personal information is not shared with your visitors. 

**Information we need from you**  
In order to establish your private ImageEvent account, we need some personal information from you when you sign up:

  * Username 
  * Your Name 
  * E-mail address 
  * Password (to sign in to your own account) 

Only your username will be shared with your visitors. You may change how you like your username to be viewed. Your email address must be valid and only be used by you. 

When you order prints, our partners need the information of:

  * Name
  * E-mail Address
  * Mailing address (to ship the prints to you or to the person(s) you choose) 
  * Billing name and address (for verification purposes only) 
  * Credit card number and expiration date 

ImageEvent is not held responsible on the information given in our partners in ordering prints. Please refer to their privacy policy.

If you want to share images with friends, you need to enter their e-mail addresses. ImageEvent will e-mail the people you select and invite them to come to ImageEvent to view your images..

**Sharing your images**  
By default, Sharing your ImageEvent does not require a password. You may choose to add a password for improved privacy. Your albums are only shared in the public gallery by your explicit action. Users viewing your albums do not need to be a registered user to add a comment or sign the guestbook if you chose to have that option enabled.

**Privacy Protection**  
We realize the importance of keeping your images as private and password protected as possible-- that is why you have several options. You can decide to keep your ImageEvent Personal in your account. A Personal ImageEvent will not appear on your Home page or on any links but is directly accessible using the full url. For added protection to your albums, you can add password protection. When visitors access your Album, it will prompt to them to enter a password.

Your Home page can also be password protected. Your Home page lists all the albums in your account. When visitors visit your Home page, it will prompt them to enter a password.

**Passwords**  
Your account is protected by a password. You choose a password when you first start an account with us. Do not share your password with anyone else.

Your password needs to:

  * be between 6 and 32 characters long 
  * not be a word in the dictionary 

**Service announcements**  
We will only send you site and service announcement updates with important information about the service. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements.

**Surveys**

We may occasionally request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and email address). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the ImageEvent service.

**Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that your browser receives from Web sites and stores on your computer's hard drive. Information in cookies includes preferences you select while visiting a particular Web site. For example, by storing cookies on your hard drive, you'll return to a specific Web site with the same settings you used on a previous visit.

ImageEvent never saves information such as your password or your credit card number on cookies. We do require cookies in order to manage and protect your ImageEvent session. Cookies are used to store your e-mail address (so you don't have to type it in every time you log in) and your name (so you dont have to write it everytime you add a comment).  If you have cookies turned off, you will not be able to use many features of the ImageEvent service.

**Links To Other Sites:**

This site may contain links to other sites. ImageEvent is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these linked sites, because their privacy practices may differ from ours.

**Log files**  
Our servers store IP addresses for all connections to the service. This data is analyzed in the aggregate for administration purposes and is not linked to your personal account. Occasionally, we may use the IP logs to gather information that might help Customer Support respond to an inquiry by you about your account, but will not do so without an initial action by you.

**Legal exceptions to the rules**  
Only in the case of our good-faith belief that the law requires it or, to protect your or ImageEvent's rights or property, will we disclose customer information to proper law enforcement authorities even though you might have sent us an e-mail requesting that we don't share your information. This information may be necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone who may attempt to cause injury to another's rights or property.

**Staying current with your information and our policies**  
ImageEvent will do our utmost to keep all your information up to date, and to guard your privacy by continuously evaluating the enforcement and nature of our policies.
